Adrian B. Tagayom

Blk 20 Lot 16 P2 Winward Hills, Subd. Dasmariñas City, Cavite, Philippines \$\&\tau_{+63} 976 371 3021\$

github.com/Aeiddius

A mechanical engineering fresh graduate and front-end web developer with skills emphasizing in machine design, hvac, solidworks 3d cad design, and 4 years of programming. Though lacking in many places as a fresh graduate, I am a fast learner and willing to adapt to new technologies and knowledge.

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Mechanical Engineering: Creative problem-solving, strong analytical skills, solidworks CAD design, autocad, HVAC design, lathe machine, milling machine, drafting & interpretation of mechanical drawings, GD&T, basic electronics, arduino uno,

Programming

- Languages: python, javascript, typescript, lua, c#, c++, arduino, html
- Styling: css, scss, less, boostrap, styled components
- Frameworks: vue.js, react, nuxt3, jquery,
- **Backend**: node.js, express.js
- **Database:** sql(mysql), nosql(mongodb)
- Others: electron, neutralinojs, godot, git, figma
- Python libraries: numpy, pandas, matplotlib, scipy, scikit-learn, beautifulsoup, selanium, jupyter notebook

Softwares: Microsoft office suite, excel, matlab, ni multisim, adobe photoshop, adobe premiere, krita

Soft Skills: Excellent communication, quality over quantity, collaborative, fast-learner, proficient english writer and speaker

Interest: Philosophy, epictetus, game design, eldercrolls lore, writing novel

WORK EXPERIENCE

KUY Corporation

July 2022 – Aug 2022

Practicum Trainee

Cavite Economic Zone, Rosario, Cavite

Worked as a Machinist. Assisted in the fabrication of machine parts and interpretation of mechanical drawings. Utilized lathe, milling, drill, cnc lathe & milling, and other variety of machines to produce mechanical parts of a reflow oven machine.

EssayShark.com

December 2022 – Present

Freelance Programmer

Work From Home

Working as a Freelance Programmer dealing with student assignments, laboratories, and projects ranging from web development to python programming and to C++ coding. Handled clients from highschool, undergraduate, and master class.

• Completed 51 client orders with a total of 9.8/10 of customer rating.

EDUCATION

Lyceum of the Philippines University - Cavite

Graduated August 17, 2023

Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering

General Trias, Cavite

Student GPA: 1.65 (1.0 Highest – 5.0 Lowest)

- Coursework included Machine Design, Powerplant Eng., Industrial Eng., and Airconditioning.
- Took coursework in basic electronics, dc and ac machinery, and electives in mechatronics.
- Designed an Automated Solarpowered Waterwheel Waste Collector System for our thesis.
- Has designed a 132 TOR Air-Cooled Chilled Water Air Conditioning And Ventilation System for a Proposed 5 Story School Building in Tagaytay, Cavite.
- Final Round Participant of Computrend's SolidWorks Solid Mania 2023

AFFILIATION

Junior Philippine Society of Mechanical Engineers

LPU Student Chapter

4th Year Representative (2022 – 2023)